http://kamatoz.com/privacy.htm

Password Manager Software - PassMonster
Productivity software business organizer - MindIT!
Business productivity software - WorkManager Pro
Freeware operating system (OS) control tool - AbsoluteControl
Freeware strong encryption tool - MegaCipher 3
ARTICLES
Interested in technical aspects of modern computing? Read our articles on various aspects of utilizing computer power to serve our needs:
Personal information management
Lost Password?
Free Password Manager
Security Software
Password Management Software
Password Manager
Why Keep Passwords Protected?
Store Passwords Secure
AFFILIATES & RESELLERS
Become our affiliate or authorized reseller to start making money today! Get commisions up to 50% on each sale of our products.
Affiliates centre
LINKS ELSEWHERE
Создание, раскрутка и сопровождение интернет-магазинов
Welcome to official web site of Kamatoz.Computing, makers of the world famous password and security software, cost-effective personal information management solutions and innovative productivity tools!
PassMonster Password Manager
Version: 2.25
License: Shareware
Price: $24.95
Site licensing: YES
Volume discounts: YES
Supported OS: Windows 98 \ Me \ NT \ 2000 \ XP \ Vista
Product options:
:: More information
:: Download FREE trial
:: Purchase via RegNow
:: Purchase via ShareIt
:: FEATURES ::
mixed 256-bit / 128-bit encryption
multiple user password files support
support for encrypted & non-encrypted password files
additional security options: wipe files, protect memory
skinable interface with additional skins download
automatic update of password manager software
hidden / stealth mode (so noone knows you run a password manager)
built-in password files backup system
import to and export from most popular password storage formats
:: ABOUT ::
PassMonster is here to help you store and manage your passwords effectively! PassMonster performs the insurmountable task of storing, protecting and managing your passwords allowing you to click once and get all the password-related information you need without having to be afraid of data vulnerability.
PassMonster features easy to use interactive interface and you should only need 5 minutes to figure out how it works. Talking interfaces PassMonster is skinable! It is always nice to have a chance to customize the appearance of a program you use every day.
Want some more? How about encrypted and plain text passwords database, Stealth operation mode (so that nobody knows you run a passwords manager), multi-user support, configurable rules-dependent password generator, data backup and program access logging for strong security environments? Impressed? Then go ahead and download FREE trial now!
MindIT! Personal \ Business Organizer
Version: 3.30
License: Shareware
Price: $29.95
Site licensing: YES
Volume discounts: YES
Supported OS: Windows 98 \ Me \ NT \ 2000 \ XP \ Vista
Product options:
:: More information
:: Download FREE trial
:: Purchase via RegNow
:: Purchase via ShareIt
:: FEATURES ::
multiple alarms with sound / music / MP3
multiple task schedules
talking alarm clock for audial informing of current time
SWATCH InternetTime (tm) support
atomic time syncronization (precision up to .0000001 of a second)
holidays and observances database with customizable reminders updated via Internet
world times, GMT, time zones, local times - invaluable for travel
accounting for online time / traffic / expenses
access to Windows' hidden features
full-blown utility package including resolution switches, restarting/hibernating/rebooting with one click or one key press
clean-up of history, recent documents, visited web sites and other traces
online & offline privacy protection
minimizable to system tray, includes advanced mouse & keyboard access to all features
patented InfoTip(tm) technology offering all vital information in one baloon tooltip without even need to click an icon
full customization, friendly interface, complete support of Windows Vista
hundreds of features of expensive software in one affordble product
:: ABOUT ::
Personal information manager and multimedia organizer featuring talking alarm clock, multiple alarms and task schedules,
automatic atomic time synchronization, Swatch InternetTime support, holidays and observances reminder with database updatable via Internet,
one click access to system tools and Windows hidden features, password revealing\hiding, CTRL-ALT-DEL blocking,
one click system shutdown or reboot and much more...
WorkManager Pro - Business Productivity Software
Version: 2.0
License: Shareware
Price: $19.95
Site licensing: YES
Volume discounts: YES
Supported OS: Windows 98 \ Me \ NT \ 2000 \ XP \ Vista
Product options:
:: More information
:: Download FREE trial
:: Purchase via RegNow
:: Purchase via ShareIt
:: FEATURES ::
simplify your everyday computing by organizing applications, documents and URLs into handy Works
add unlimited number (full version only) of executables, documents and Internet addresses to each individual job
start a Work with single click
switch between Works easily
choose, say, 'accounting' and let it load 5 Excel sheets, 3 Word documents, open the stocks site and run accounting application
updates itself automatically via Internet
:: ABOUT ::
As seen on TechTV!
WorkManager Pro productivity software lets you automate working with multiple tasks on a PC. With this handy tool you can arrange as many tasks (programs, documents, URLs and system commands) as you need into one Work. Once this is done, the Work can be run with just one click. Just imagine clicking once and getting your browser, mail program, messenger, all your favorite URLs run and open in a second!
AbsoluteControl - Freeware Windows Control & Tweaking Tools
Version: 2.30
License: Freeware
Supported OS: Windows 98 \ Me \ NT \ 2000 \ XP \ Vista
Product options:
:: More information
:: Download full version
:: FEATURES ::
control Windows settings with just a click
switch screen resolutions easily with one click and automatically set the highest possible refresh rate
open & close multiple CD & DVD drives with a single click on task tray icon (handy when you have little kids and disable the button to avoid damaging the drive or hurting your children)
advanced computer power management
reboot, shutdown, poweroff, hibernate or suspend your PC with just a click
search the web with a variety of serch engines - you choose which to use with a single click
manage system startup list easily - add or remove applications with two clicks
view comprehensive report on system memory load, available disk space and resources usage by simply hovering mouse pointer over an icon in tray
absolutely freeware (no nags, no ads, install and use) and will stay freeware forever
updates itself automatically via Internet
:: ABOUT ::
As seen on TechTV!
AbsoluteControl (tm) system control software offers wide range of OS control tools available on single click.
It can set your screen resolution with highest possible refresh rate, open\close your CD drives, reboot, shutdown, poweroff, hibernate and
send to standby mode your system. Web-search available with one click! AbsoluteControl monitors memory usage providing you with most
up to date information without the need to perform even a single mouse click. AbsoluteControl handles ALL Microsoft operating systems,
runs in background and is capable of automatic updating. The destribution size is 192 kb only including comprehensive illustrated help system!
MegaCipher 3 Freeware Strong Encryption
Version: 1.28
License: Freeware
Supported OS: Windows 98 \ Me \ NT \ 2000 \ XP \ Vista
Product options:
:: More information
:: Download full version
:: FEATURES ::
encrypt unlimited number of files with strong patented encryption algorithm
decrypt files on any system
340,282,366,920,938,463,463,374,607,431,770,000,000 possible combinations
requires more than 100 years of modern PC to pick password using bruteforce
does not slow down system operation, encrypts files on the fly
send encrypted file together with MC3 executable to your communication partner or give him / her a download link
does not rely on Microsoft's system Crypto API which means there is no way to fool the encryption / decryption module
monitors memory sniffing during encryption process to prevent sniffers
runs on any Windows system
does not include 3d-party code, modules or dependencies
absolutely FREEWARE! will stay free FOREVER!
:: ABOUT ::
MegaCipher data encryption software allows on-the-fly encryption of all kinds of data with 128-bit open keys.
Encrypted data can only be decrypted with the correct password. The key cannot be found with brute force attack as it can have
340,282,366,920,938,463,463,374,607,431,770,000,000 possible combinations!!! Now you can safely hide your private data
from others eyes!
Kamatoz.Computing
SUBSCRIBE TO NEWS
What's this?
Privacy Policy
SPECIAL OFFERS
We always have some HOT special offers for you! Discounts, giveaways, freeware, enchancements, t-shirts and much more...
Check them out...
CONTACT US
Click here to contact us
OUR PARTNERS
You can purchase shareware password manager software, productivity software or system control tools via:
LINKS ELSEWHERE
Создать интернет магазин
Optimized for 1024x768. Best viewed with Firefox or Internet Explorer.
Copyright © 1999-2007 Kamatoz.Computing | Privacy Policy
Last updated: 01.10.2015
